Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Family Collected Papers, circa 1880s-1989, undated IA20009
Institutional Records and Archives
- Photographs, circa 1880s-1970s; Series III.; 2.4 Linear Feet (7 boxes containing over 100 unique images)
  - Getty residences:
    - South Kingsley Drive interior (?), undated; (3 photographic prints) (Box 2010.IA.17-06)
    - South Kingsley drive exteriors and interiors, including teenaged J. Paul Getty in the Chadwick, 1908; (approximately 16 photographic negatives) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set A)
      Several of these images are blurred or otherwise of poor quality.
    - Color photographs of Sutton Place interiors, exteriors, and grounds in different seasons, undated; (approximately 37 photographic prints and corresponding negatives) (Box 2007.IA.32-01)
    - Sutton Place with Cadillac in driveway, undated; (2 photographic prints) (Box Shared 1986.IA.48-12; 2002.IA.02, Folder 6)
    - Getty home at East 61st Street and 5th Avenue, which was torn down to clear the site for the Hotel Pierre (New York), circa 1920s; (1 photographic print) (Box 1986.IA.48-11)
  - Business:
    - Rural scenes with people, horses, and oil derricks in background, undated; (5 photographic prints, sepia and black-and-white) (Box 2010.IA.17-06)
    - Aerial photos of Mexican coast, including Acapulco, where Getty's Hotel Pierre Marques would eventually be constructed, undated; (8 photographic prints) (Box 1986.IA.48-11)
    - Oil tanker (?), undated
      - Print, (1 photographic print) (Box 2010.IA.17-06)
      - Negative, (1 photographic negative) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set C)
  - People:
    - Tintype of unidentified boy on a tricycle, undated; (1 ferrotype) (Box 2010.IA.17-06)
    - Snapshots of unidentified persons, undated; (approximately 18 photographic prints) (Box 2010.IA.17-06)
    - Unidentified woman at beach, in front of auto, and on the deck of a boat, undated; (approximately 4 photographic negatives) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set C)
    - Unidentified woman in front of equine statues and stone columns, undated; (2 photographic negatives) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set D)
    - Unidentified woman with dog (on tennis court?), undated; (1 photographic negative) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set G)
    - Unidentified woman shipboard, undated; (2 photographic negatives) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set H)
    - Group photo (unidentified persons), undated; (1 photographic print) (Box Shared 1986.IA.48-12; 2002.IA.02, Folder 7)
  - Other:
    - Exteriors and interiors of unidentified buildings, undated; (13 photographic prints) (Box 1986.IA.48-11)
    - Space-age stewardess leaning over passenger (film or television?), undated; (1 strip of 3 black-and-white negatives) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set I)
    - Red-haired woman in nursery rhyme costume on stage with boy, undated; (1 color negative) (Box 2010.IA.17-06, Section Set I)